Guide to the Jon Lewis Photographs of the United Farm Workers Movement
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Books and Audiovisual Materials, 1967-2009; Series II; 2.25; (6 boxes)
  - Materials by Others
    - Farmworker Movement Documentation Project
      - CD-ROMS, 2004 August 30-2009 December 29
        - Jon Lewis Scanning @ 4,000 dpi with corrections 1 - 62 10.10.08, 2010-wa-34440-0063; 1 (Box 51)
        - JON LEWIS 1. EL TEATRO 2. BOYCOTT 3. PEOPLE'S BAR, 2010-wa-34440-0064; 1 (Box 51)
        - CONTACTS + BOYCOTT GAYLORD LEWIS, 2010-wa-34440-0065; 1 (Box 51)
        - César + Dolores, 2010-wa-34440-0066; 1 (Box 51)
        - [no label information], 2010-wa-34440-0067; 1 (Box 51)
        - Jon Lewis 77 Photos @ 300 dpi RGB, Grayscale, & Re-Sized for the Web CD 12.29.09, 2010-wa-34440-0068; 1 (Box 51)
      - Ink jet prints from digital surrogates, circa 2004-2009 (Box 53)
      - Postcards, circa 2008 (Box 48, Folder 121)
      - Songs of the Farmworker Movement (Hermosa Beach, Calif.: Sand Flea Studios) [Sound Recording], 2008 (Box 48, Folder 122)
    - Bill Brummel Productions, Viva La Causa: The Story of César Chávez and a Great Movement for Social Justice (Montgomery, Alabama: Teaching Tolerance), 2008; Running Time: 48:00 (Box 54, Folder 123-126)
      This documentary film uses contemporary footage and dramatic reenactments to depict the grape strike and boycott.